

#### CONTACT

- +63 917 105 4231
- weigilauron@gmail.com
- https://weigilau8.github.io/resume/
- s we.jicc
- © Goldenville Subd Banawa Cebu City ph, 6000

# **SKILLS**

**Adobe Photoshop** 

Adobe Illustrator

HTML / CSS / Bootstrap

PHP / Laravel / Wordpress

Javascript / Vue / React

GIT / MongoDB / MYSQL/Shopify

#### REFERENCE

## Ronan Antony Padillo,

Sr. Software Engineer

Accenture Inc Ebloc2 IT Park, Lahug +63 932 658 6241

## Brian Dave Bautista

Facilities, Safety and Security Manager Ramon Aboitiz Foundation Inc. +63 32 411 1700

# LUIGI JOSE LAURON

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

I'm adaptive to change and is open for new learnings and opportunities. I've learned and is still learning new things in IT and everything in its orbit. I'm fascinated with web programming, (e.g. building websites.)

I started as a Graphic Designer at JAPAN INTERTRADE CALLCENTER (JICC), after 2 years I applied Graphic Designer at Shima later on I was absorbed and hired as a front-end developer which helped me with the beginning of my career.

I am looking for a company where I can grow my career, do my craft and where I can work as a front-end developer.

It would be a great opportunity for me to offer you my commitment and my passion for my work, if I'd be given a chance to be part of your wonderful team.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### JPHAT Solution Inc.

Web Developer

Sept 2018 - Mar 2020

- Maintaining Wordpress websites
- Update and add new functionalities
- Implemented website, Mobile applications and landing pages from concept through deployment
- Collaborated with Japanese team to implement new feature developments.

#### SHIMA BPO Inc.

Front-End Developer

Nov 2013 - Aug 2018

- Maintaining and update all client "Offer Pages Sites".
- Troubleshooting bugs and adding new features
- Redesign wordpress template from PSD(code from the scratch)
- Knowledge in Fillezilla. GIT version control
- Develop a payroll system of the company using Vanilla PHP, Bootstrap.
- Fixed front end bugs (HTML, CSS, Javascript errors (JQUERY)

## JAPAN INTERTRADE CALLCENTER (JICC)

**Graphic Design** 

Mar 2011 - Nov 2013

## **EDUCATION**

## **Informatics College**

Web Development Apr 2018 - May 2018

**Tesda Certification** 

Relevant coursework: HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP(CRUD, Framework)

## **Cebu Institute of Technology**

BSBA - Marketing Management

2005 - 2009

Bachelor's Degree